pornmd.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy Policy | PornMD

#### Last Modified: 16 May 2018

#### INTRODUCTION

MG Freesites Ltd (hereinafter "we", "us" or "our") operates the website [www.pornmd.com](https://www.pornmd.com/) (hereinafter "PornMD" or the "Website" or the "Platform") and is the controller of the information collected or provided via this Website.

This Privacy Policy (together with our Terms of Use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with applicable privacy and data protection laws and regulations. Please read this privacy policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By using our Platform, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. If you do not want your information to be processed as set out in this privacy policy, please do not provide any personal data to us and do not use the Platform.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this privacy policy for information on how to contact us.

#### WHEN THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES

This privacy policy applies to information we collect:

  * on the Platform; or
  * in e-mail and other communications between you and the Platform.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * any other website operated by us (or our affiliates and group companies)
  * any website operated by a third party; or 
  * any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Platform.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE COLLECT IT

We only collect a limited amount of information by which Users may be personally identified ("Personal Information").

When you access our website from a mobile device like a tablet or phone, we receive information about your approximate location from your IP address, information about your device, including one or more unique identifiers for your device, and your mobile carrier.

Information collected automatically:

Information about your computer and internet connection. This includes your internet protocol address ("IP address"), your country of location (so we know which version of the website to display), operating system and browser and platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Macintosh platform) and language, access times and the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us.

Information provided by cookies (or browser cookies). Cookies are small text files that are stored in your web browser or downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie, and allow a website to recognise a user's device.

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you, which we have grouped together as follows:

  * Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website.
  * Profile Data includes your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, if applicable, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.
  * Usage Data includes information about how you use our Website, products and services.
  * Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We do not collect special categories of Personal Information about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences. However, depending on how you use our Website and services, your Personal Information may include information that allows drawing conclusions about your sex life or sexual orientation ("Sensitive Personal Information"). The collection, use and disclosure of such Sensitive Personal Information is necessary to provide some of our service to you.

#### PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us for following purposes:

  * Provision of services: to present our Platform and its contents to you and to provide you with information or services that you request from us;
  * Functionality and security: to diagnose or fix technology problems, and to detect, prevent, and respond to actual or potential fraud, illegal activities, or intellectual property infringement;
  * Compliance: to enforce our terms and conditions and to comply with our legal obligations;
  * Consent: for any other purpose with your consent provided separately from this privacy policy; and 
  * As informed: in any other way we outline when you provide information to us.

#### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We understand that your Personal Information is important and we therefore want you to understand the circumstances in which we disclose it as well as other information we have collected about you or your activities on the Platform. We do not share your personal information with third parties except as indicated below:

To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganisation, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Users is among the assets transferred. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to ensure that the entity to which we transfer your personal information uses it in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy.

In response to a summons or similar investigative demand, a court order or other judicial or administrative order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement, government or regulatory agencies; or to enforce our Platform terms and conditions or other agreements or policies; or as otherwise required by law (including responding to any government or regulatory request). In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us, in our sole discretion.

To the extent a disclosure is necessary in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, report or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to maintain and protect the security and integrity of our Platform or infrastructure.

To the extent this is necessary to fulfil any other purpose not mentioned above for which you provided personal information and, if applicable, your consent separately from this privacy policy.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. In particular, we may transfer non-personal information and process it outside your country of residence, wherever the Platform, its affiliates and service providers operate. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources.

#### HOW WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The information that we collect about you, including Personal Information, will be stored and processed in the countries in which we and our third parties service providers maintain facilities.

By using the Platform you consent to the transfer of information that we collect about you, including personal information, to any country in which we, our affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this privacy policy.

#### RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

To the extent we have collected your personal information for purposes of provision of services and customer management, we keep it for as long as you have an account with the Platform, and as needed to provide you with our respective services.

If you delete your account, or if your account is closed for any reason or visit our Website, we retain your information to the extent this should be necessary to comply with have legal, auditing or account obligations or it is in our archive system and cannot be separated from other information. Where possible, your Personal Information will be anonymized.

Personal Information used for functionality and security purposes will be stored as long as necessary to ensure the proper operation and the security of our Platform and services.

The period for which we keep your personal information that is necessary for compliance and legal enforcement purposes varies and depend on the nature of our legal obligations and claims in the individual case.

#### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to safeguard your Personal Information from unauthorised access and disclosure. For example, only authorised employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorised persons from gaining access to your personal information.

The safety and security of your personal information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Platform, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You must not to share your password with anyone. We are not responsible for circumventions of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Platform.

#### CHOICES ABOUT HOW WE COLLECT, USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We have outlined below some of your choices regarding the Personal Information you provide to us.

You can choose not to provide us with certain Personal Information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our Website.

You may at any time, update, correct or delete certain personal information that you have provided to us by contacting us at the email address/contact form provided in the Website.

You may refuse to accept cookies from any source at any time by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse cookies. Further information about the procedure to follow in order to disable cookies can be found on your Internet browser provider’s website via your help screen. You may wish to refer to allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html for information on commonly used browsers.

You may delete your account at any time. If you do so, your Personal Information and any and all other account related information including, but not limited to, user profile data, sharing data and any other data, or content specifically associated with your account, if any, will no longer be accessible by you.

After deleting your account, if you want to create a new account, you will have to sign up again as none of the information you previously provided or saved within your account will have been saved.

#### YOUR RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Subject to local law, you have certain rights regarding the Personal Information we collect, use or disclose and that is related to you, including the right

  * to receive information on the Personal Information concerning we hold about you and how such Personal Information is used (right to access);
  * to rectify inaccurate Personal Information concerning you (right to data rectification);
  * to delete/erase your Personal Information (right to erasure/deletion, "right to be forgotten");
  * to receive the Personal Information provided by you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit those Personal Information to another data controller (right to data portability)
  * to object to the use of your Personal Information where such use is based on our legitimate interests or on public interests (right to object); and
  * in some cases, to restrict our use of your Personal Information (right to restriction of processing).

#### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify or revise our privacy policy from time to time. Although we may attempt to notify you when major changes are made to this privacy policy, you are expected to periodically review the most up-to-date version found at [www.pornmd.com](https://www.pornmd.com/), so you are aware of any changes.

If we change anything in our privacy policy, the date of change will be reflected in the "last modified date". You agree that you will periodically review this privacy policy and refresh the page when doing so. You agree to note the date of the last revision to our privacy policy. If the "last modified" date is unchanged from the last time you reviewed our privacy policy, then it is unchanged. If the date has changed that means that there have been changes. In these circumstances you agree to re-review our privacy policy and your continued use of our Platform confirms your acceptance of the revised terms.

All changes are effective immediately and apply to all access to and use of the Platform thereafter. The updated version of our privacy policy supersedes any prior versions immediately upon being posted.

#### COMPLAINTS PROCEDURE

We regularly review our compliance with this privacy policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or our treatment of personal information by contacting us at [support@pornmd.com](mailto:support@pornmd.com). When we receive a formal written complaint, it is our policy to contact the complaining party regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information that cannot be resolved by an individual and us.

#### NO RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES

This privacy policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties.

#### NO CHILDREN

Our Platform is not intended for use by persons under the age of 18 and we do not intentionally collect Personal Information from children. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [support@pornmd.com](mailto:support@pornmd.com). If we become aware that a child has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to remove such information and terminate that person's account. We delete the personal information of anyone who our age verification procedures suggest is under 18 years of age.

#### NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE

We do not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy.

#### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us at [support@pornmd.com](mailto:support@pornmd.com).

You may also write to us at MG Freesites Ltd, 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540, telephone us on +357 22662 320 or fax us on +357 22343 282.
